Now we've got a spec command in place, let's use it to spec out a new feature for this project.The feature I want to spec to begin with is the authentication forms, because currently the signup and login pages are pretty empty.If we take a quick look at those, which are both inside the public group, you're going to see that the only template inside them is currently a title for the page.
現在我們已經建立好 spec 指令了，讓我們用它來為這個專案規格化一個新功能。 我想先規格化的功能是身份驗證表單，因為目前的註冊和登入頁面相當空白。 如果我們快速看一下這些頁面——它們都在 public 群組裡—— 你會發現裡面唯一的範本目前只有頁面的標題。
So what I'd like to do is make a spec for adding a form to each page, login and signup, and a link to switch between each one as well.I also don't want to implement any actual authentication logic at this stage and only focus on the front end for now.So then let's come to the chat and use the spec command first of all.And remember, in order to see this command after you make it, you'll need to exit your Cloud Code session, then resume it again to pick it up, which is what I've already done.
所以我想做的是為每個頁面（登入和註冊）新增一個表單規格， 以及一個可以在兩者之間切換的連結。 我也不想在這個階段實作任何真正的身份驗證邏輯，現在只專注在前端部分。 那麼讓我們來到對話框，先使用 spec 指令。 記住，建立這個指令之後要看到它，你需要結束目前的 Claude Code 工作階段， 然後重新開啟才能載入，這也是我已經做過的事情。
Anyway, after the spec command, I'm just going to paste in this single prompt which says.Let's spec the authentication forms on the login and signup pages.They need e-mail and password fields, a hide password icon, and a submit button (signup login).The forms should only log details to the console for now when they are submitted.We should be able to easily switch between the two forms.
無論如何，在 spec 指令後面，我要貼入這段提示： 讓我們為登入和註冊頁面的身份驗證表單建立規格。 它們需要電子郵件和密碼欄位、一個隱藏密碼圖示， 以及一個提交按鈕（分別標示為「註冊」和「登入」）。 表單在提交時目前只需要將詳細資訊輸出到主控台。 我們應該能夠輕鬆地在兩個表單之間切換。
Now we could also manually add the login and sign up pages as context using the at symbol if we wanted to.But for this project we probably don't need to because it's quite small and currently there's not many pages to look through to find them.All right then, so let's press enter and see what happens.I'm going to also toggle on auto accept.
當然，我們也可以用 @ 符號手動將登入和註冊頁面加入作為上下文，如果你想的話。 但對這個專案來說可能不需要，因為它很小，目前沒有太多頁面需要找。 好的，讓我們按下 Enter 看看會發生什麼事。 我也要開啟自動接受（auto accept）。
And it's checking the branch first of all to make sure we have nothing to commit.And now it's come up with the feature title, authentication forms, the feature slug right here with a dash, and then the branch name, which is how we specified it.Claude first, then feature, then the name of the feature using the feature slug.All right, cool.So now it's switched to the branch as well using this bash command.And then it's going to go ahead and create this file, which it's done.
它首先在檢查分支，確認我們沒有任何需要提交的變更。 現在它生成了功能標題「authentication forms」、帶連字號的功能 slug， 以及我們指定格式的分支名稱——先是 claude，再來是 feature， 然後是用功能 slug 命名的功能名稱。 好，很棒。它也已透過這個 bash 指令切換到了那個分支。 接著它去建立這個檔案，而且已經完成了。
And if we take a look over here inside the specs folder, we can see that new file.Awesome.All right, so let's just have a quick look at the spec file it's generated then.So we have the title at the top, then the branch name, then we have a quick summary, which is basically what we wrote as a prompt.It's reworded it.And then down here we have some functional requirements.
如果我們到 specs 資料夾裡看，就能看到那個新建立的檔案。太棒了。 好的，讓我們快速看一下它產生的規格檔案。 頂部有標題，然後是分支名稱，接著有一個簡短摘要， 基本上就是我們輸入的提示，它換了個說法。 再往下有一些功能需求。
So e-mail input field with appropriate type and validation attributes, password input field with toggle visibility functionality, hide show password icon, submit button labeled login on the login page, sign up on the sign up page, submission handlers, logs to the console, blah, blah, blah, accessible form labels.And then, if we scroll down, I'm doing this very quickly, by the way, because I'm quite aware you don't want to watch me just reading this out, but definitely read through this yourself.I would spend 5 or 10 minutes just going through this.
包含適當 type 屬性和驗證屬性的電子郵件輸入欄位、 帶有切換可見性功能的密碼輸入欄位、顯示／隱藏密碼圖示、 登入頁面標示為「登入」的提交按鈕、 註冊頁面標示為「註冊」的提交按鈕、 表單提交處理器、輸出到主控台等等，以及無障礙表單標籤。 接著如果我們往下捲動——我現在做得很快， 因為我很清楚你不想看我一直唸這些，但你自己一定要仔細讀過一遍。 我自己會花個 5 到 10 分鐘把這個看完。
Possible edge cases, so when a user submits the form with an empty e-mail field, okay, or empty password or invalid e-mail.A user rapidly toggles the password visibility, blah, blah, blah, accepts its criteria down here.So these are things that kind of have to pass, I guess, for it to be acceptable.So e-mail and password fields render correctly.The password visibility toggle icon changes state and reveals or hides the password text.
可能的邊緣情況： 使用者在電子郵件欄位空白、密碼欄位空白或電子郵件格式無效的情況下提交表單； 使用者快速切換密碼可見性等等。 往下是驗收標準，這些是要能通過才算合格的條件： 電子郵件和密碼欄位正確顯示； 密碼可見性切換圖示在狀態改變時正確顯示或隱藏密碼文字。
Yeah, these all seem pretty good.Then we have some open questions.And these are questions that Claude Code wants to ask us to kind of clarify certain things about this feature.So for example, should we validate e-mail format before allowing submission?So we could do that or we could leave it to the back end.Let's just say light validation.
嗯，這些看起來都不錯。 然後我們有一些開放問題， 這些是 Claude Code 想詢問我們以釐清某些功能細節的問題。 例如，我們是否應該在允許提交之前驗證電子郵件格式？ 我們可以這樣做，或者把它交給後端處理。 就說做輕量驗證吧。
And should we enforce minimum password length requirements?We're not going to do that on the front end because I'm going to let the back end handle that later on when we use Firebase.So we'll say no for now.Should form inputs persist when navigating between login and sign up?Okay, so if we type an e-mail address out, should it stay there if we're toggling between them?I don't think we really need that functionality.Do we need remember me checkbox?No, we don't need that.
我們是否應該強制要求密碼最短長度？ 前端不做這個，因為之後使用 Firebase 時我會讓後端來處理。 所以現在就說不需要。 在登入和註冊之間切換時，表單輸入值是否應該保留？ 也就是說，如果我輸入了一個電子郵件地址，切換頁面後它還會在嗎？ 我覺得我們不太需要那個功能。 需要「記住我」核取方塊嗎？不，我們不需要。
And then should we include forgot password link?No, we're not going to include that either.All right then, so we've been through all those questions, and then finally we've got some testing guidelines for when this feature is actually created later.So it's told it to create the test folder, or rather the test file in the test folder.and create tests for these things right here.So again, I'm not going to spend much longer now on this because I want to move ahead to the next step, which is implementing this feature.
然後，我們需要加入「忘記密碼」連結嗎？不，這個也不加。 好了，我們已經看過所有這些問題， 最後還有一些測試指南，是之後實際建立這個功能時要用的。 它告訴要在 test 資料夾中建立測試檔案，並為這裡的這些項目建立測試。 同樣地，我現在不打算在這上面花更多時間， 因為我想繼續進行下一步，也就是實作這個功能。
But I would definitely normally spend a lot more time going through this spec, making sure everything is correct, editing where I don't think it's correct before moving on.So then now we've made a spec file for a new feature, and the next step is to make a detailed technical plan to implement this feature using Claude Code's plan mode, which we'll see in the next lesson.
但正常情況下，我一定會花更多時間仔細審閱這份規格， 確認所有內容都正確，並在繼續之前修改我認為不正確的地方。 好的，現在我們已經為一個新功能建立了規格檔案， 下一步是使用 Claude Code 的規劃模式， 為實作這個功能制定詳細的技術計畫，我們將在下一堂課中看到。